Anirudh Sharma

Jaipur, Rajasthan 302001 anirudhsharma0350594_9nq@indeedemail.com +91 62624 30350

Hello, my name is Anirudh Sharma, a finance graduate. I have an overall experience of 2 years in the field of Operations Management.

Along with that, I possess some skills; Project management, Client relationship management, Financial analysis, Financial modeling & valuations, MS Office, MS Excel, Tableau, and SQL, and working more on my skills to enhance my performance.

I am very greedy to learn new things and apply them practically. So, that I can work more effectively and efficiently.

Currently looking for a Full-time Job in the field of Operations. As I want to make a career in this domain and that is why I've decided, that in the future, I'll go for a distance learning MBA program from NMIMS with my ongoing job to gain more knowledge in Operations.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 2000-02-06 Eligible to work in: India

Highest Career Level: 1-2 years experience

Industry: Accounting, Administrative Assistance, Analytics, Automotive, Banking & Finance, Business Operations, Export, Import, Insurance, KPO, Research, Analytics, Management, Oil & Gas, Energy,

Power, Infrastructure, Project Management, Strategy, Management Consulting Firms

Total years of experience: 2

Work Experience

Operations & Research Intern

Accrete LLC

January 2022 to July 2022

- Researching complex financial and economic topics
- · Working with the latest AI technology and exceptional people & making it a reality
- Providing feedback to the machine learning model
- Validating outputs from current models & suggesting improvements
- Managing a group of interns and projects.

Operations Intern

G&MN Investors - Remote July 2021 to January 2022

- Client relationship management.
- Responsible for scrutinizing the financial statements and other public documents of an organization.

- Analyzing proper estimation of the financial worth of a particular Organization.
- I was also responsible for managing portfolios/ funds and gauging the level of risks involved in an investment.
- In-depth Equity Research and analysis.

Financial Research And Operations

Wellspring Consultancy - Remote November 2020 to July 2021

- Develop LBO and DCF models
- 3 statement analysis and valuation.
- In-depth research and analysis on Mergers and Acquisitions
- Strategic planning

Operations Intern

Chetak Enterprises Pvt. Ltd. - Neemuch City, Madhya Pradesh September 2020 to November 2020

- In-depth market research and analysis
- Build strategies, roadmaps, and research papers
- Provide feedback and advisory for proper implementation
- Formulate new prices, offers, and E-commerce initiatives
- Customer research to understand trends

Education

Bachelor's in Business administration (finance as an elective)

Amity University, Jaipur - Jaipur, Rajasthan

August 2019 to June 2022

Skills / IT Skills

- Microsoft excel (5 years)
- Business communication skills (3 years)
- Financial modeling and valuation (2 years)
- SQL (Less than 1 year)
- Fundamentals of digital marketing (Google digital garage) (2 years)
- Financial Analysis (1 year)
- Financial Management (2 years)
- MS Office (5 years)
- Operations Management (2 years)
- Project Management (2 years)

Languages

• English - Fluent

- German Beginner
- Hindi Expert

Certifications and Licenses

Business communication skills

July 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3fnSPyS

Completed four weeks of online certified training on Business Communication Skills. The training consisted of Introduction to Business Communication, Essential Communication Skills.

Financial Modeling and Valuations

September 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3I1LCRc

Completed a six-week online certified training on Financial Modeling and Valuation. The training consisted of Understanding Excel, Investment Decision Techniques, Application of Decision Techniques, Financial modeling, and valuation.

Financial Analyst Certification

December 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3FCbCRO

Here I learned in-depth analysis of financial statements, pivot tables, financial forecasts, ratio analysis, DCF models, financial statement analysis, strategic planning, corporate finance, financial analysis, Microsoft excel, financial modeling, and financial accounting.

Fundamentals of digital marketing

July 2021 to Present

Digital marketing is one of the best courses in today's business world and Google's digital marketing course provides us all the best knowledge that one should have for digital marketing like, SEO, SMM, and many more

Data Analytics with Excel

November 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3GvUT3R

Successful completed and passed the National Association of State Boards of Accountancy (NASBA) Examination with 78 percentile through LinkedIn Learning.

Here, I learned the advanced formulas and the practical aspects of Data analysis with MS Excel.

Excel Analyzing and Visualization Cash Flow

November 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3latipk

In-depth analysis of cash flows in excel to perform ratio analysis, DCF modeling, calculate FCF, Terminal value, and so on

Human Resource Management

July 2021 to Present

https://bit.ly/3KbpMfX

Completed an eight weeks online certified training on Human Resource Management. The training consisted of Introduction to HRM, Manpower Planning and Job Analysis, Recruitment and Selection, Remuneration and Compensation Management, Training and Development, Performance Management System, Labour Laws, and Statutory Compliances, Disciplinary Procedure, Employee Engagement, and HR Branding, Human Resource Information System (HRIS), Introduction to HR Analytics, Communication and Business Acumen and The Final Project modules. In the final assessment, I scored 73% marks.

LOR Accrete.ai Operations and Research Intern

January 2022 to Present

Researching complex financial and economic topics
Working with the latest AI technology and exceptional people & making it a reality
Providing feedback to the machine learning model
Validating outputs from current models & suggesting improvements

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1k1rarj51PjN4UUZxMbRL9k3_JcemoXgf/view?usp=sharing

Operations management

January 2022 to Present

- · Data processing.
- Risk analysis and strategic planning.
- Budget and staff management.
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving.
- Time management and Organizational management.

NGO, Non-Profit / Student Organizations

Jankalyan Yojana

July 2021 to July 2021

I was selected as an fundraising and public relations intern at Jankalyan yojana (it's a NGO) working for the poverty of our nation as in supplying food items, clothes, and accessories and even our NGO had provided medicines in this pandemic where the poor people wasn't able to buy the medicines who were being going though this covid-19 situation.